https://www.crownbattery.com/privacy-policy

Products
Product Search
Applications
Power House Cleaners
Power.Match.
Resource Center
All Resources
Brochures
SDS & Compliance
Safety.First.
Power House Cleaners
Power.Match.
Resource Center
All Resources
Brochures
SDS & Compliance
Safety.First.
Crown battery Privacy Policy
We at Crown Battery are committed to your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit www.crownbattery.com (the “Site”).
IMPORTANT INFORMATION
Changes to the privacy policy
We periodically update our privacy policy to ensure that all information is up-to-date and accurate. We encourage you to review this privacy policy periodically.
Contact us
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or other questions about the privacy of your information on the Site, please contact us by email at info@crownbattery.com or by mail at 1445 Majestic Drive, Fremont, Ohio 43420-0990 USA
TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED ON THE SITE
We collect the following types of information about you, collectively known as “Personal Information.” Please note that your information is stored in the United States in secured data centers, and may be distributed to other countries as determined by your contract or by necessity, as detailed below.
Information that you provide directly
Crown Battery asks for information directly from visitors to the Site such as emails, names, company information, and phone number via optional forms. This information is securely stored in the HubSpot CRM (Customer Relationship Management).
Information provided by your device
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.” Device Information may include:
Cookies information: Cookies store and convey a modest amount of specific data regarding your internet browsing behaviors on the Site. Cookies used by the Site may be stored with identifying information and used to create a more personalized experience. Cookies are not a security risk, as they information they contain is specific to behavior on individual websites and not your identity, but you can manage, delete, and block cookies easily via your browser’s settings.
Log files: Log file information is automatically reported by your browser or mobile device each time you access the Site. When you use our Site, our servers automatically record certain log file information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.
Analytics information
We collect “Analytics Information” directly or using third-party analytics tools to improve the user experience on the Site. This information is collected in aggregate, and cannot be reasonably used to identify any specific Site visitor.
Information about children
The Site is not targeted towards or intended for children under the age of 13, and we do not intentionally or knowingly collect the information of children under the age of 13. If you believe we have collected the information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us at info@crownbattery.com so that we can delete the information.
HOW YOUR INFORMATION IS USED
The information that we collect from Site visitors is only retained in our systems for as long as reasonably necessary to perform the uses detailed below. You may contact us to obtain a copy of or request deletion of your Personal Information, unless our retention and processing of the information is necessary for safety and security, as detailed below.
For the performance of a contract
When processing your order, we collect and share your payment information (credit card information, debit card information) with credit card companies and other payment providers. Crown Battery does not store any payment information after the transaction has been completed. We also share your shipping information with our shipping and communications provider, who may contact you regarding the status of your order.
Your information may be used over the course of any contract you make with Crown Battery to provide customer service, support, and answer questions about our services.
To supply useful information, offers, and other marketing and promotion
Where we have your consent, we communicate with you via email in order to provide you with helpful informational content, information regarding our products or services, surveys, offers, promotions, contests, and information regarding relevant changes to operations at Crown Battery. We share your information with third-party marketing services who assist us in the creation and implementation of email marketing campaigns. You may always choose to unsubscribe or change which types of information you’d like to receive via email in your email preferences, which can be accessed at the bottom of every email you receive from Crown Battery We also use your information to display advertising on social media or other platforms and websites you enjoy. These cookies may be deactivated as described above.
For legitimate business interests
We are always seeking to improve the online experience of our Site visitors by making the Site useful and easy to use. To do so, we use Device Information and Analytics Information to determine typical Site usage in order to inform changes to the Site. We also monitor aggregate customer interactions with the Site and theCrown Battery brand as part of our efforts to measure and benchmark the success of our marketing efforts and business goals.
For safety and security
We reserve the right to use or disclose your Personal Information if required by law, or if we reasonably believe that use or disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or comply with a law, court order, or legal process.
1.419.334.7181  /  sales@crownbattery.com
Address:
